<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Getting Started on Check Point CloudGuard Network Security Workshop - AWS GWLB</title>
    <link>/01gettingstarted.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Getting Started on Check Point CloudGuard Network Security Workshop - AWS GWLB</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language><atom:link href="/01gettingstarted/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Logistics</title>
      <link>/01gettingstarted/2_wsarch.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01gettingstarted/2_wsarch.html</guid>
      <description>Workshop Logistics AWS GWLB Reference Architecture Diagram Notes: There are several different ways to organize your AWS architecture to take advantage of CloudGuard Network Security(CGNS) traffic inspection with AWS GWLB. It is important to remember that as long as the traffic has a symmetrical routing path for forward and reverse flow, the architecture will work. This diagram may look complicated at first glance because it covers ALL Traffic Flow Options. For each scenario, we will highlight the components involved in that flow.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>GWLBe Options</title>
      <link>/01gettingstarted/3_gwlbeoptions.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01gettingstarted/3_gwlbeoptions.html</guid>
      <description>AWS GWLBe Options Distributed Architecture The Distributed GWLB Architecture features an IGW and GWLBe in each VPC. Accordingly, the ingress &amp;amp; egress Internet traffic from that VPC use the local IGW.
Centralized Architecture The Centralized GWLB Architecture connects VPCs together with TGW and use a Centralized Ingress and Egress from either
Combined Security VPC (as we see in this workshop) Dedicated Internet VPC attached to TGW (not covered in this workshop) </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Initial Setup</title>
      <link>/01gettingstarted/5_securitypolicysetup.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01gettingstarted/5_securitypolicysetup.html</guid>
      <description>Initial Setup (Credentials and Check Point Security Policy Setup) Preparing the environment NOTE: The below steps assume you are performing this workshop as part of an AWS Immersion Day&amp;hellip;if you wish to run this in your own environment you can simply run the following CloudFormation Template manually: CGNS GWLB CFT
Browse to the AWS Event Engine link that was provided, Accept Terms and Login Select the Email One-Time Password (OTP) option&amp;hellip;it is recommended to send the OTP to a personal email address to avoid potential expiration of the OTP due to corporate security controls.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Test Host Login</title>
      <link>/01gettingstarted/6_testhostlogin.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01gettingstarted/6_testhostlogin.html</guid>
      <description>Testing Procedures Login to test EC2 instances The test EC2 instances are secured by inbound GWLB flows. To access the instance, you will need to use the Load Balancer DNS names and EC2 Private keys provided in the CloudFormation Output
Use the DNS name above to login via SSH(using Putty or Terminal) with the Private key provided to the following EC2 instances…be sure to note the special port being used for the DB and Shared Services instances</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tips and tricks</title>
      <link>/01gettingstarted/7_tipstricks.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/01gettingstarted/7_tipstricks.html</guid>
      <description>Tips and Tricks Helpful Items AWS Load Balancing&amp;hellip;including GWLB AWS Blogs for GWLB Check Point SK for GWLB Architectures Repetitive testing tool for AL2 CLI: Apache Benchmark yum install httpd-toolsfor i in {1..100}; do ab -n 1000 -c 100 http://www.google.com; done Gateway Load Balancer Limitations &amp;amp; Considerations Flow Stickiness Currently GWLB flow hashing default 5 Tuple (TCP) and 4 Tuple (UDP) Multi layered protocols may be hashed differently Currently flows are sticky for their lifetime.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
